<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-25T15:01:51-05:00</updated><id>https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Evan’s Journal</title><subtitle>This is my personal blog where I share content about things going on my life.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Date Night</title><link href="https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/date/night/2020/01/25/date-night.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Date Night" /><published>2020-01-25T14:03:39-05:00</published><updated>2020-01-25T14:03:39-05:00</updated><id>https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/date/night/2020/01/25/date-night</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/date/night/2020/01/25/date-night.html">&lt;!-- Featured Image --&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
   &lt;img src=&quot;https://github.com/evy0311/blog/raw/gh-pages/assets/images/2020-01-25-date-night-1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Content --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, Gena and I went out on a date night. We try to make it a thing to go out on a nice date atleast once a month, sometimes more. This is a great way for us to unwind, relax, and catch up on everything that has been going on in each other’s busy lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to go to Melt Bar and Grilled, a really cool restaraunt that we’ve been to before. Melt has awesome food, of which they are most known for their grilled cheese. We got ready and took off, makingo ur way through the crappy, rainy weather that Columbus has brought upon us for this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrive, thankfully at a decent hour with no wait. While walking in, the most memorable part of our night occured: Gena fell. Not just a trip and fall, but she fell for a solid ten seconds. I think her heals coupled with the fact that the floor was wet are what caused this, but it was too funny to not mention here. She’s okay, and thankfully never made it all the way to the gorun (a kind stranger helped me catch her). But I definitely did not let her forget about this, as we laughed randomly throughout the night about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite thing to get at Melt is their Mac and Cheese grilled cheese. It is one of the most interesting foods I have ever eaten, and one of the most American foods you can think of. Add Bacon, and you’re set! For those that haven’t been to Melt, I highly recommend it, as their food, service, and atmosphere are awesome!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we finished up at Melt, we made our way to Simply Rolled Ice Cream, where we both enjoyed chocolate fudge ice cream. We also made a stop at our favorite little store in Columbus, Rocket Fizz. All of these establishments are located in the Short North Arts District, which is my favorite part about Columbus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this was all said and done, we made our way back to the dorms to watch a movie with some of our friends. “Ex-Machina” was the movie of choice, of which none of us had ever seen before. It was a really good movie, and really interested me since it is highly centered around AI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, last night was an amazing night. Gena and I both lead very busy lives with school and work, so setting time aside to spend with one another is always a treat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my blog!</title><link href="https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/blog/new/2020/01/22/welcome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my blog!" /><published>2020-01-22T13:43:39-05:00</published><updated>2020-01-22T13:43:39-05:00</updated><id>https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/blog/new/2020/01/22/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.evanhorsley.com/blog/blog/new/2020/01/22/welcome.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello, friends! Today I am taking the plunge and have decided to start removing myself from certain social media websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This decision has been a long time in the making, especially because I use sites like Facebook to connect with other family members. However, I have been spending too much time on these things, and often get stressed out due to the content on them. These sites are a great way to connect with family and friends, but I have decided to remove myself from them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest part of my decision in this entire thing was I want to make sure my family and friends are still able to stay in touch with me and see what I am doing in my life. Therefore, I am moving all of the content I normally would post on Facebook, etc., to here. This will be my blog that I write on occasionally showcasing cool things I’ve gotten the chance to do, life updates, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still in the process of setting it all up. I need to setup comments, setup notifications, and configure the theme and layout a bit more. This shouldn’t take too long, but I’ll likely write about it in an upcoming post for those of you that are new to this sort of thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, I’ll still have my phone and phone number, so those of you that have it can always reach out whenever. For those that have questions, feel free to reach out to me via e-mail currently here: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:evan@evanhorsley.com&quot;&gt;evan@evanhorsley.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that moving away from sites like Facebook not only removes a factor of stress in my life, but also frees up more time to spend with people, too. I love hanging with friends and family in person, and want to remove distractions such as Facebook from my life so I am able to do those things more. Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello, friends! Today I am taking the plunge and have decided to start removing myself from certain social media websites.</summary></entry></feed>